ILGWU. Independents. Out-of-Business Contracts, 5780/147
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Sherman MFG Co. (Darlington, South Carolina), 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Shields Industries, Inc. (Lowell, Massachusetts), 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Ship 'N Shore Inc. (Hazleton, Pennsylvania), 1964-1981 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Sidney Bernstein and Sons (New Holland, Pennsylvania), 1968-1993 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Simmons Canada, Inc. (Cornwall, Ontario), 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Simpson Street Cutting (Luzerne, Pennsylvania), 1989-1994 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Skaff MFG Co., Inc. (Lowell, Massachusetts), 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Sparrow Cutting (Nazareth, Pennsylvania), 1983-1994 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Spartan Undies Division of United Merchants (Spartanburg, South Carolina), 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Sterling Stall (Winnipeg, Manitoba), 1980-1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- State Pleating Co., Inc. (Boston, Massachusetts) [Folder 1 of 2], 1965-1992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- State Pleating Co., Inc. (Boston, Massachusetts) [Folder 2 of 2], 1965-1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Sue-Deb Garment Co. (Toledo, Ohio), 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Surrey Classics (Vancouver, British Columbia), 1976-1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Swanknit, Inc./Layettes, Inc. (Cohoes, New York) [Folder 1 of 2], 1959-1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Swanknit, Inc./Layettes, Inc. (Cohoes, New York) [Folder 2 of 2], 1959-1987 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Tamac MFG Corp. (Tamaqua, Pennsylvania), 1984-1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Tejidos De Coamo (Coamo, Puerto Rico), 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- USA Garment Co. (Cadillac, Michigan), 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- US Slide Fastener Corp. (Boston, Massachusetts), 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- United Belt (San Francisco, California), 1977-1982 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Vag Le Pret A Coiffer Inc. (Montreal, Quebec), 1989-1992 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Vanessa MFG Corp. (New Bedford, Massachusetts), 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Victor Bias Binding Co., Inc. (Boston, Massachusetts), 1972-1991 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Virginia Apparel MFG (Amelia and Jetersville, Virginia), 1991-1994 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- V'Lora Swimwear, Inc. (Bloomfield, New Jersey), 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Vogue Corset (Montreal, Quebec), 1964-1967 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Weather-Rite, Inc. (Secaucus, New Jersey), 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Wellhart MFG Co., Inc. (Fall River, Massachusetts), 1990-1991 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- West Helena-Helena Sportswear Co. (West Helena, Arkansas), 1976-1986 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Wonder Maid, Inc. (Washington, Missouri), 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Worcester Knitting Co. (Worcester, Massachusetts), 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Youthcraft Coat and Suit Co., Inc. (Kansas City, Missouri), 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 25)